voidu.com 2019-05-13

# Privacy Policy

You are visiting voidu.com, which is part of the online network of Azerion, a gaming company.

We are based at Beechavenue 182-200, 1119 PX Schiphol-Rijk, The Netherlands. You can contact us at [privacy@azerion.com](mailto:privacy@azerion.com). You can contact our Data Protection Officer at [dpo@azerion.com](mailto:dpo@azerion.com). In this Privacy and Cookie Notice, we describe how we use cookies and process data, including personal data, when you visit a site within our network.

Voidu’s Website Privacy Policy provides clear and concise information on how visitors' information is collected, processed, and stored. It describes the types of data gathered and how this data is protected, as well as the way communication from third parties to Voidu is treated.  

**We are committed to a lawful, fair, and transparent processing of personal data, adhering to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).**   

**Kinds of data and purposes of processing:**  

**1\. We process the following (categories of) personal data**

Name

We collect the given names (first name, family name) of customers, and company name, names of job applicants, and names of contacts when they express interest in our services and/or sign up for our newsletter or create a user account on our web portal.

Email address

We collect the email address of customers, job applicants, and contacts when they express interest in our services and/or when they sign up for our newsletter, or create a user account on our web portal.

Telephone number

We collect the phone numbers of customers, job applicants, and of contacts when they express interest in our services or when they sign up for our newsletter.

Address

We collect address details for those users who create user accounts on our portal. This information is key for determining geographical[Office1]  area and regional release information for our content.

Gender

We collect gender details with our user account details, as this enables us to offer[Office2]  our users more specific tailored content and to generate accurate statistical data.

Date of Birth

We collect date of birth details as an age verification, so that only age-appropriate content is delivered.

IP Address

Your IP address is utilized to confirm your geographic region and geolocation. IP addressing is also utilized to determine which products are available to users within specific regional areas.

**2.  ** **What (purposes) do we use the data for**

We use the data listed under (1) to offer five services:

  * Exclusive Events Registration and other marketing and promotional programs;
  * Job applications;
  * A newsletter we periodically send to all our subscribers. We also add emails[Office3]  that we obtain from general inquiries to this list. Within each newsletter email, an opt-out link is provided;
  * User Account Management: We manage user accounts on our portal based on the user information provided. This includes Name, email address and physical addressing information, geographic region, and age details. This enables us to provide and track user preferences with regard to content and to provide regional localized content;
  * Financial Data: our payment vendors process your financial data, when you make a purchase through our website.

**3.  What is our legal basis for processing this data**

We base our processing on consent of the data subject for the newsletter and user account profiles, the execution of a contract with the data subject for customers, and legitimate interest for job applicants. For job applicants, our legitimate interest is to have a pool of job applicant data that is current and complete.

**4.   Where do we obtain the data from (sources)**

We collect the data through forms submitted via our website, general inquiries by email, contact information provided at business meetings and in business dealings, and information in CVs submitted by job applicants. However, we do not advertise job openings directly on our website.

**5.   How long and where do we store data**

We collect the data through forms submitted via our website, general inquiries by email, contact information provided at business meetings and in business dealings, and information in CVs submitted by job applicants. However, we do not advertise job openings directly on our website.[Office4] [J5] 

  * We store customer information for at least 7 years to be able to meet our obligations to keep accurate records for the tax authorities;
  * We store newsletter subscriber information until a subscriber indicates they no longer want to receive the newsletter;
  * We store job application information for up to 10 years;
  * We store user account data until the user opts to decommission their account.

**6.   What safeguards have we taken to protect data**

Taking into account the nature, scope, context, and purpose of the processing, we have taken the following technical and organizational measures:

  * Voidu employs an infrastructure of geolocated tenants to ensure that collected data remains within the legal jurisdiction of the region where it was collected;
  * Defense in depth methodologies are employed to ensure that all data storage resides within secured VPNs with strict access controls in place;
  * Encryption technologies are utilized to ensure the confidentiality and integrity of data at rest and in transit;
  * Active security monitoring is employed within our physical infrastructure. We actively monitor the security of our database but may need to rely on our partners and trade affiliates to notify us of any data breaches.

**7.  Who we share data with**

We do not actively share data with any third parties other than processors acting on our behalf. We require that these companies adequately safeguard your personal data, and that they do not use your data for any purpose not authorized by us.

Voidu may disclose information collected from the website to its various offices across the world. However, they are only allowed to use the information collected on the websites for internal purposes. 

We have included a Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Google+, and Pinterest button and pixel on our website to enable users to integrate with their social media profiles as and when they see fit to do so. Such parties may capture some of your data that way. Please refer to their respective privacy pages for more information on how they may collect and use your data, including any personal data.   
For information regarding the precise use of cookies, other similar tracking technologies, and personal data by Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Google+,[Office6] [J7]  please refer to their respective policies:

Facebook - [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php)  
Twitter - [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy)  
LinkedIn - [Privacy Policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy)  
Google+ - [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=ZZ)

Voidu works with a number of advertising partners and providers to facilitate the digital advertising visible on our website. We share the above data with a number of buyers, such as advertisers, brands, media agencies, and other intermediaries, although not all buyers receive the same data. The list of buyers changes on a continuing basis, and for this reason, we cannot include a comprehensive list here.

  * Google - [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=ZZ)
  * Microsoft - [Privacy Policy](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement)
  * Criteo - [Privacy Policy](https://www.criteo.com/privacy/corporate-privacy-policy/)
  * CJ - [Privacy Policy](https://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy)
  * Daisycon - [Privacy Policy](https://www.daisycon.com/en/privacy/)
  * TradeTracker - [Privacy Policy](https://tradetracker.com/privacy-policy/)
  * Idealo - [Privacy Policy](https://www.idealo.co.uk/privacypolicy.html)
  * TradeDoubler - [Privacy Policy](http://reports.tradedoubler.com/pan/displayTextKey.action?textKey=CMS_PUBLIC_162_CONTENT&)
  * Link Connector - [Privacy Policy](https://www.linkconnector.com/privacy-policy/)
  * ESV Digital - [Privacy Policy](http://www.esvdigital.com/cgu/)
  * Perfect Audience - [Privacy Policy](https://www.perfectaudience.com/privacy/)
  * VE - [Privacy Policy](https://www.ve.com/privacy-policy)

When you make a payment or purchase on the Voidu website, your financial data is processed by one of our authorized payments vendors, as is determined by your selected payment method. Voidu utilizes the following payment vendors. For further details on how they handle your data please visit the vendors’ website directly.

Wirecard - [Privacy Policy](https://www.wirecard.com/privacy-policy/)  
PayPal - [Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/en/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)  
iDEAL - [Privacy Policy](https://www.ideal.nl/en/disclaimer-privacy-statement/)  
P24 - [Privacy Policy](https://www.przelewy24.pl/eng/privacy-policy)

**8.  Transfer of your personal data**

Please be aware that within the provision of our services, Voidu transfers data to third parties. In some cases, these third parties may not be based within the European Union, which means that this includes data transfer outside of the EU borders. Where and whenever such a data transfer is required, we will do so only when we have put in place appropriate safeguards to protect your personal data. Please contact us to get a copy of the safeguards that we have put in place. Our contact details are listed at the top of this page[Office8] .

**9.  Cookies on Voidu's websites**

Cookies are small pieces of information (small files) that a website leaves on your equipment (e.g. your computer). The website instructs the web browser with which you view websites (e.g. Internet Explorer) to store these cookies on your equipment. On Voidu's websites, three kinds of cookies are used:

**Functional cookies:**  
Functional cookies are necessary to make a website function. Voidu uses functional cookies to facilitate navigation on the websites and to store specific user settings or user preferences to optimize your use of the websites.

**Analytical cookies:**  
Voidu uses analytical cookies (including pixel tags) in order to measure, by means of the software of third parties like Google Analytics, how many visitors the websites get, which parts of the websites receive the most views, and what percentage of news recipients reads the online mailings. The statistical information collected is used to customize the contents of the websites or online mailings to the needs of visitors or readers in the best possible way.

**10.  Voidu’s Cookies**

We use the following cookies:

**Name**

| 

**How long**

| 

**Placed by**

| 

**Reason**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
Voidu.customerAffiliate

| 

90 days

| 

Voidu.com

| 

Functional: To allow for the tracking of Affiliates  
  
Voidu.customer

| 

1 year

| 

Voidu.com

| 

Tracking: User behavioral and interest tracking  
  
**Third-Party Cookies**

Our partners use the following cookies:

**Name**

| 

**How long**

| 

**Placed by**

| 

**Reason**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
__atu

| 

256 days

| 

AddThis

| 

Sharing through social media  
  
_seg

| 

1 year

| 

Segmentify

| 

User tracking  
  
_sgf

| 

1 year

| 

Segmentify

| 

Personalized content  
  
__ar_v4

| 

persistent

| 

Google Analytics

| 

Conversion tracking for ads  
  
_ga

| 

persistent

| 

Google Universal Analytics

| 

Maintain anonymized client identifiers  
  
__cfduid

| 

1 year

| 

LinkConnector

| 

Identify trusted traffic  
  
MUID

| 

1 year

| 

Microsoft

| 

Unique user tracking  
  
Anj

| 

3 months

| 

Nexus

| 

Cookie synchronization  
  
pa_

| 

2 years

| 

OpenX

| 

Advertising effectiveness tracking  
  
uid

| 

1 year

| 

ESV Digital

| 

Activity gathering data  
  
cto_Iwid

| 

13 months

| 

Criteo

| 

Personalized retargeting  
  
LCUTS

| 

per session

| 

LinkConnector

| 

Conversion tracking  
  
__auc

| 

1 year

| 

Alexa Analytics

| 

Collect information on consumer behavior[Office9]   
  
fr

| 

3 months

| 

Facebook

| 

Advertising products  
  
uuid2

| 

3 months

| 

Google Tag Manager

| 

Registering user device  
  
**11.  ** **Your rights**

You have the right to request access to your personal data that we process. You also have the right to:

– Rectify incorrect personal data or erase it in certain circumstances; 

– Restrict or object to the processing of your personal data; 

– Receive your data so that you can use it elsewhere (data portability).

Where we process data based on your consent, you also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time but we would like to point out that this does not affect the lawfulness of the processing before the date that you withdrew your consent. You can manage your consent on the following webpage: <https://www.voidu.com/customer/info>

If you wish to exercise any of the above rights, please contact us at privacy@orangegames.com. Finally, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. If you do not know who your supervisory authority is, please contact us and we will tell you.

**Version**

Our Website Privacy Policy was most recently updated on October 30, 2018[Office10] .

**Questions**

We welcome comments and suggestions regarding the Voidu privacy notice. Please send questions about our privacy policy or the information we have collected from you to privacy@orangegames.com.
